WELCOME
M
Hold it, Akino.
Hmm?
What do you have there?
Umm...
GIRLS  BATH
A cat.
I can tell that!
And what are you planning to do with it?
We're going to take a bath!
Did you forget that's against the rules?
No! Give it back!
Onii-chan's bullying me, he's a kidnapping demon!
This is why you're not getting anywhere with the goddess!
I haven't even seen her lately.
Maybe she's avoiding me?
What do I need to do?
I don't even know when she'll show up or where to find her.
What are you two doing?
Causing trouble again?
We could hear you down the hall.
Onii-chan's bullying me.
No, I'm not!
Akino was going to take this cat into the bath with her,
and I stopped her from doing so.
Oh, that cat!
It's the same one from before.
Remember? When we were doing preparations last week?
Really?
It's a regular customer, then.
Even so, it's just common sense to keep animals out of the bath.
Do you want to run off all our customers?
Does it have a cold?
It'd feel better if we warmed it up in some hot water.
That's a good idea.
Yep, it is!
Well, let's take it into the bath–
Hold on.
It can't go in yet?
No. I mean, wouldn't a bath just for cats be okay?
That's what I had in mind all along.
First we need to make the water the ideal temperature for cats.
It's a bit too cold.
Were you planning to boil it for dinner?
I guess I put in too much power.
We can't seem to get it right, huh?
So we need bath water of the perfect temperature?
Oh!
Wait here, I'll be right back.
Can you do it, Tokura-san?
Umm... I'd like to try too,
but this little one's fallen asleep.
Tokura-chan's pillows have the same
healing effect as a hot spring, don't they?
Thanks for waiting!
Good afternoon.
Umm...
Did you need me to help with something?
Shirahane-san.
You're way too beautiful!
Wow!
As expected of the goddess.
It's nothing. I'm glad I was able to help everyone.
What are you doing?
Since the water's ready, I thought I'd get in too.
You're really...
Oh my!
Cats are gathering.
Maybe they all love hot springs?
There sure are a lot of cats.
Pardon me.
I just thought all the cats meowing together...
was really adorable and cute.
Y-You're the one who's cute!
Tokura-chan's pillows!
The bath water the goddess made feels really good.
Thanks for helping us out today.
Thanks, Goddess!
No, your words are far too kind.
I'm glad the Hot Spring Goddess allowed this.
Akino would've had trouble mending these cats by herself.
Geez, Mitomo!
I'm really glad that Tokura-chan made us remember.
Our relaxing with the cats is fine since we're not open this season.
I'm happy that everyone's having a good time.
So you're both male?
Oh well.
I'm fine being anywhere in bath water prepared by Shirahane-san.
WELCOME
M
Everyone, is the water temperature okay?
YUMEKURI
It's the best!
WELCOME
M
NATURAL HOT SPRING
Hmm?
Let's meet again someday, okay?
NATURAL HOT SPRING
FIN~